A child?
There's one more thing you should know.
The majority of previous bloodsport champions
have died during their final matches.
I heard the duke running
the bloodsport colosseum
arranges for the champions
to be at a disadvantage.
Eve Speed is the undefeated champion
and tremendously popular.
Management would almost certainly
want to kill her to pass the
baton to the next generation.
Which means we'll be stopping
that tomorrow, right?
No, that's not my intention.
There's no need for us
to politely wait until the day of.
TOGETHER WITH THE LORD OF FLIES
Did you need me for something?
I came here to talk with you, Eve Speed.
I thought I already told you I don't
know where the Witch of Taboos is.
That was a lie, right?
You're a rude man.
You indebted to the witch?
No.
That was a lie just now.
And who are you?
Why don't we stop trying
to deceive each other, Eve Speed?
Tell me what you're after.
I want to save you.
"Save" me?
The duke running the show will make sure
you go down in tomorrow's match.
Why would you help me?
Because I can't have someone with intel
on the Witch of Taboos dying on me.
Is kidnapping the girl you brought to Monroy
and fleeing tonight not an option?
Why you!
If you dare lay a finger on that girl...
I just wanted you to know I'm
aware of your situation.
We know you've been fighting
for Lis's sake these past two years.
I appreciate the warning about the plot.
However, I can't afford to run
from tomorrow's bloodsport.
Why not agree to kidnap her and flee?
Where would we flee to?
Unless I play by the rules
to gain her freedom,
Duke Zuan will hunt us down,
the guild running the colosseum
will put up a bounty,
and mercenaries across the
continent will come after us.
It'd be one thing if it were just me,
but I can't do that to that girl.
What if I know a good place to hide?
Where the Witch of Taboos lives.
You could have her shelter you two.
Impossible.
No one can reach the heart
of the Land of Monsters.
- The heart?
- I told you, it's not the kind of place
you just waltz into.
- She's talking like she's been there before.
If we work together,
we might able to reach it.
I promise to protect that girl
to my fullest ability as well.
So, how about it?
Are you willing to wager on us?
Your swordsman seems to have
martial training, but you...
Despite appearances, I'm skilled with magic.
I'm good enough I managed to defeat
a Skeleton King with ease.
Those are certainly fierce,
but they're nothing compared to what
lies within the Land of Monsters.
Then what if I told you I was the
one who killed the Five Dragoons?
Impossible.
I don't know if this will
convince you, but...
Paralyze!
My body...!
You shouldn't try to move.
If you force it, you'll begin
bleeding from various places.
Absurd!
Precisely.
This absurd power is what allowed a
weakling like me to kill Civit Gartland.
Allow me to provide additional proof.
I'm Seras Ashrain, the one the
Five Dragoons were pursuing.
I witnessed their deaths with my own eyes.
It's up to you whether you believe us.
I just wanted to demonstrate my power
DISMISS (HEAD)
- I just wanted to demonstrate my power
- to prove myself to you.
You certainly have.
However, it's to no avail.
Either way, I must face my
bloodsport match tomorrow.
I won't go to the Land of Monsters.
That remains unchanged.
I will seize our freedom with my own hands.
Victory in bloodsport has always
been my path forward.
Besides, I can't fully trust you two.
Even though my liege wishes to save you?
Would you believe someone
you'd only just met that day?
In contrast, bloodsport and I
have a long history together.
Well, that's to be expected.
Still, even if you win the match,
do you truly believe Duke Zuan
will keep his word?
What?
He sounds like a scumbag from
what I've heard about him.
I find it hard to believe he'll
honestly just grant you your freedom.
I know he's not a very upstanding man.
But the fact is that he's always honored
his end when I produced results.
The duke is still human.
I doubt he's as heartless as you claim.
You're naive.
Between you two and the world of bloodsport,
it's obvious which I should trust more.
I'll keep my faith in bloodsport.
Why, Eve Speed?
Why do you keep insisting
you believe in bloodsport?
What?
Are you sure you aren't saying it
in order to convince yourself?
I know I've said a few rude things,
but I'll genuinely be praying
for your victory tomorrow.
- Let's go.
- Y-Yes.
Wait! Why are you—
We plan to leave the city
early tomorrow morning.
We'll be at the bridge by the big front gate.
You should come if you change your mind.
My apologies.
I revealed my identity without asking.
In the end, it made our
argument more convincing.
I'm not concerned about it.
Did something happen here?
Those in this home have been cursed
for the sin of defying Sir Muaji,
progeny of the curse god.
Muaji?
The Five Dragoons fell to our curses!
- The Five Dragoons fell to our curses!
- They say the man of the house
was foaming at the mouth
- We are the saviors of Ulza!
- and clawing at his throat as he died.
I'm sure he must have been cursed.
How scary.
I find myself outraged at their insolence.
It seems like those guys
genuinely believe their group
took out the Five Dragoons.
- genuinely believe their group
- P-Please stop this!
Consider it an honor.
You've been chosen by us.
It's a glorious thing.
Now, come along quietly.
Please! Please let go of me!
This simply won't do.
We must take you to Sir Muaji and beg for him
to show you his blessing
and reform your heart!
Don't lay a hand on them.
Berserk.
Hey! Stop!
- What's gotten into you?!
- Dark. Berserk. Berserk.
Dark. Berserk. Berserk.
Y-You too?!
What the hell is going on here?!
Right.
Roughly four hours until time's up.
Do you think there's a future
where she wins their freedom and
lives peacefully with that girl?
Nope.
From what people have said, Eve's owner,
Duke Zuan, is a piece of shit.
There's no bright future
for her with him around.
I'd never trust someone
I deem to be a scumbag.
So long as Eve Speed remains
a good, honest person,
there is no happy ending for her here.
Not until someone comes along with a poison
strong enough to counteract
the poison already eating away at her.
I've more than fulfilled my
obligations to Duke Zuan.
He should be satisfied.
Surely he'll show mercy
in honor of my contributions.
I'm only going to confirm that.
To confirm that I'll be free
if I win tomorrow.
Then I'll be rid of this doubt.
I imagine tomorrow will be a grand event
with Eve Speed's final bloodsport match.
Yes.
We don't have any other bloodsport
warriors so beloved by the crowd.
See? They aren't plotting any—
So, Eve Speed will die as planned, yes?
Of course.
Per tradition, we'll give her
a paralytic before the match.
The goblet of purification?
That was a great idea.
DUKE ZUAN
- I've already given that mangy pseudo-human
plenty of chances to shine.
I've already given that mangy pseudo-human
Yet she's still a beast in the end.
Let's have tomorrow's victor
skin her hide and wear it.
Wonderful idea!
We can sell them as the Leopard Slayer!
Well, what about that dark elf
at the Whiteleg Tavern?
Eve kept at bloodsport much longer
than we planned thanks to her.
So what are your plans?
Will you be granting her
freedom as an act of mercy?
Actually, I'll be taking her in.
Oh? Showing some compassion?
She's just a childish brat right now,
but she'll be an incredible beauty one day.
I plan to thoroughly train her myself.
If I tire of her, then I'll simply
sell her off to a whorehouse.
Still, haven't you spent a
long time with Eve as well?
Have you no sympathy for her?
Now that's an odd thing to ask.
How could I ever develop any sympathy
for a subhuman animal?
Duke Zuan...
You're truly a brute so vile?!
Unless I rescue her,
there is no escape for her.
Lady Eve Speed.
Hmm?
I'm looking forward
MUAJI
ASHINT'S LEADER
- to tomorrow's bloodsport match.
Yeah.
So this is where you were!
Sir Muaji!
There's been some trouble...
Have they left already?
You're earlier than I expected.
If you're here, then...
Yes, it was exactly as you said.
So, are we bringing that girl with us?
Of course.
I can't afford to leave her here.
Then can I assume you're going
to the Land of Monsters with us?
I have my terms, but I intend
to tell you where the witch lives.
Then it's settled.
Now, let's get to kidnapping.
Lis!
You're still cleaning that spot?
You're so slow!
You dark elves really
are useless, aren't you?
I'm sorry...
This girl's starting to get
a little sexy too, isn't she?
Hey, you!
You'll pay if you lay a hand on her!
Someone important has already agreed
to take in this brat one day, you hear?
Tch. Damn brat, already seducing people...
Still, she's a real quiet one, ain't she?
Never smiles and never cries.
You sure she even has emotions?
You would think, but—up we go—the
brat is really just toughing it out.
There! There! There! There!
Now, I wonder how long you can endure.
She may seem unfazed,
but it's having a sure effect on her.
This is for me?
Yeah.
We'll fight together,
and together we'll win our freedom.
I need to be strong, like Big Sis.
Wasn't that a bit harsh?
I'm the one people should feel sorry for!
I'm working myself to the bone,
and no good comes of it!
What's wrong with venting a
little pent-up stress on the brat?
Tch! Already stopped her damn crying.
I know what you hate most.
Don't overdo it now.
Get a big head and I'll kill you,
you damn brat!
I'm sorry for being weak, Big Sis...
I never heard it was this bad.
Big Sis...
It's over now.
I'm taking the girl with me.
And you...
P-Please spare me!
Duke Zuan ordered me
to discipline her harshly!
If I'd refused, he would have killed me too!
I swear!
I won't say a word to anyone
about wherever you two go!
So please spare me!
The situation's changed.
We can't stay in the capital now.
It looks like I'll be taking you
with me on another harsh journey.
Would you still come with me?
Yes.
I'll go anywhere as long
as I'm with you, Big Sis.
You tell them that Eve Speed headed south
to search for Lisbeth after
she suddenly disappeared.
If you can do that, I'll spare you.
G-Got it! I absolutely will!
I'll never forget your mercy in sparing me!
Lis, I apologize for everything
I've done to you.
Please forgive me.
I can't believe I was so
harsh to such a kind child.
Thank you for everything.
Be well, Lis.
We're going.
Big Sis! Is that...
Sorry for suddenly making a loud noise.
Go on ahead.
I'll take care of some business and join you.
All right.
You may have fooled a good person like Eve,
but your shitty acting won't work on me.
Do you really think you're
going to get away with this?!
You're defying him!
It's over! For you and that mangy beast!
Serves you right!
I could tell immediately
by that girl's reaction.
It feels great to hit nearby
objects and raise hell
when you're shouting and angry, doesn't it?
But it's intolerable to
those on the receiving end.
Any loud noise sends them right back
to every time you shouted at them.
I can't stand it.
What?
I can't stand the idea of you getting
to live like nothing happened
after all the horrible things
you did to that girl.
I just told you it's all over for you lot!
I'm the only one who can save
you from that terrifying duke!
So be clear! Are you begging
for my forgiveness or not?!
I was already clear, wasn't I?
It's over for you.
Paralyze.
Dark. Poison.
Y-You monster...
Right back at you.
It won't be a great cover,
but I'll make it look like
you were a robbery victim.
If you do this, then you're
going straight to hell.
If you let me go, then you
can make it to heaven.
GATES OF HELL
- Hell? Heaven?
GATES OF HEAVEN
I'm willing to do whatever
it takes for my goals.
I've roped other people into my revenge,
and I've already crushed plenty underfoot.
You must be stupid.
We're obviously going to hell.
Both you and me.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's fine.
Hati, I'm sorry about earlier.
What happened with that woman?
I did what needed to be done.
I see.
More importantly, is the girl okay?
Yeah. Lis, introduce yourself.
M-My name is Lisbeth.
LISBETH
DARK ELF
- I'm sorry. I don't know my last name.
I'm sorry. I don't know my last name.
Oh, please call me Lis
since Lisbeth is so long.
I'm Touka.
Hati was an alias.
My real name is Touka Mimori.
And this swordswoman is Seras Ashrain.
It's a pleasure to be with both of you.
Sir Tooka...
I'll do anything.
So please let me accompany Big Sis.
Please.
We're about to head into a dangerous
place where we might lose our lives.
I don't care.
As long as I'm with Big Sis.
All right.
Thank you so much!
This has bugged me for a while,
but Tooka,
are you aware of an odd,
watery sound coming from your person?
Yeah, that's my other companion.
Companion?
Introduce yourself, Piggymaru.
A slime?
These are our new traveling
companions, Eve and Lisbeth.
I'm Eve Speed. Good to meet you.
It's nice to meet you, little Piggymaru.
I do intend to tell you where
the Witch of Taboos lives.
Though, before I do,
I'd like to hear why you want to meet her.
I have a scroll of forbidden magic
written in ancient text that's
difficult to decipher.
But I've heard the Witch of Taboos
should be able to do it.
Then you don't intend her any harm?
So long as she doesn't intend me any.
I'm a simple woman.
I can't read the far future like you can.
I can't predict everything either.
I'd like to swear myself to you.
Wow, talk about a pretty big jump in trust.
I believe you are a trustworthy man.
Your reasoning?
You could have chosen any
number of inhumane means
to get information on
the Witch of Taboos out of me.
You could have used that girl
to threaten me as well.
But you didn't.
You are a good person.
What happened to not trusting people
you only just met that day?
Trustworthiness can't be determined
by the length of time you spend with someone.
I feel like this has taught me that much.
Take my hand.
Sure.
Will it be all right to take the girl
with us into the Land of Monsters?
I'll protect her no matter what.
Whatever I have to do, I'll get
those two to the Witch of Taboos.
You truly are kind.
You think too much of me.
I have a much more pragmatic reason
for adding them to our party as well.
Which would be?
Eve has been to the Land of Monsters before,
and she has some connection to the witch.
She'll make it easier to approach the witch.
As for Lis...
They say the Witch of Taboos
is a dark elf, right?
Oh, and so is Lis.
Right. We'll be visitors who've
saved a young girl of her species.
Play our cards right and we have
ourselves a favorable introduction.
You've thought that far ahead...
Impressive, Sir Tooka.
All primarily out
of self-interest, of course...
But letting a girl like that
enjoy life with a smile
is far better than
her quivering and crying.
Yes, I agree with that.
Our pursuers are responding too quickly.
How did they find out?
I passed a man right before
leaving the bloodsport colosseum.
Who?
He called himself Muaji.
I see. That group's boss, huh?
I'm sorry.
I'm the reason you're all at risk
of such grave danger.
Big Sis?
Tooka, take Lis.
You might be a bloodsport champion,
but you have no chance
against those numbers solo.
Even so...
Besides, what good would it do us to lose
our guide to the Witch of Taboos here?
Then what do we do?
We defeat them.
I'll set a trap in advance.
Just as you predicted,
the first wave is chasing after the horses.
Were there any Ashint among them?
No, I couldn't see any.
The first wave was most likely
the duke's personal army.
Which means...
that second wave might be Ashint.
We've succeeded in dividing them for now.
Eve, you take Lis and hide
in the forest a little ways up ahead.
I'll stand and fight with you.
I need Seras for what I'm about to try next.
So who will protect Lis?
All right. I'll follow your lead.
He was sharp enough to surmise his
enemy's plan from scant information.
This Muaji guy is a smart one.
Seras.
Yes?
I understand. I'll try it.
Do you have a plan for beating so many foes?
If you can't beat a foe head-on,
drag them somewhere you can win.
Now, let's get started.
DARK PLOT ~MISSING~